I think there's absolutely no way we can
have a drawn out bare market at this at
this pace of growth because it's it's
it's not just growth of capex, it is
growth of revenues. I mean, you just saw
Open AAI go from 40 billion to 70 70
billion in like a month and a half. They
added 30 billion in ARR in a month and a
half. These numbers are actually insane.
What's up everybody? It's LG here and
welcome to Milk Road Stocks, the daily
market show. I can't believe it's almost
October that we're still talking about
Zoftware on the show, but I promise they
only talk about it for a little bit
today. Today is September 30th, 2026,
recording on the 29th. AI agents are
finally here and they might be about to
blow up the software market. OpenAI,
Meta, XAI, they're all moving
aggressively into agents and enterprise.
And now we're back to the same question
from earlier this year. Who gets
disrupted next? Meanwhile, the AI trade
still looks kind of shaky. Although
OpenAI just reported huge annual
numbers, the macro looks terrible. So
which way does all of this go next? On
today's episode, our four top analysts
debate whether SAS stocks are heading
for that massive sell-off, whether the
AI labs can actually make money on all
this growth long term, and why Micron's
earnings could tell us whether the
infrastructure boom is just getting
started. And a reminder that you can see
each of their portfolios in Milkro Pro
for just a dollar. and also catch an
exclusive 20 minute session recorded
after the episode where the guys discuss
their actual moves with each other in
Milk Road Pro After Hours. All of that
is at the link below. Gentlemen, welcome
back to a another rollup uh as usual
jam-packed with things going on uh that
we're going to talk about. Open AAI
hitting 70 billion in AR, I think, was a
surprise for a lot of people. Not so
much a surprise for me. I think if
you've been watching the show, I've been
saying very bullish OpenAI and and their
revenues, but Martin and Vincent very
they they've been bearish and uh I think
now they've they've been told off. So,
we we'll talk about that in a bunch of
other things, but let's just start on
macro because I think there's a lot of
things going on in the market at the
moment. Melvin, why don't you um Oh, by
the way, Vincent will be joining us in a
few minutes, so don't worry for those
listening. He's just running a little
bit late, but he'll be he'll be popping
in later. But Melvin, why don't you kick
us off? Uh what are you thinking in the
markets right now?
>> Sure. Yeah, we actually had a lot of
bullish news yesterday. Um, Nvidia
announcing their $150 billion buyback.
Meta pushed um Muse deeper into
enterprise and then we had SpaceX had
another major Starship milestone. But
despite all that market still finished
red yesterday and I think the biggest
reason was rates. Um the 10-year briefly
hit around 5.25. It could be higher now.
Um which is like the highest level in 19
years. Um oil remained above 92 despite
there was some major headlines going
around but despite that oil still
remained elevated. We all know higher
oil creates like more inflation concerns
and higher inflation makes um investors
like us worry that you know Fed may
increase rates on during the next um
meeting. Um and to be honest the
economic data hasn't really helped
either. Uh the reason being is that
flash PMI for September um surged to a
5-year high showing that there's like
strong economic growth and momentum. Um
and then Dallas manufacturing which came
out yesterday survey um showed the same
thing higher growth. Um and they also
said it's a higher inflation
environment. Uh what was surprising was
the consumer spending has remained
surprisingly resilient. Um but and also
the labor market has shown signs of
improvement as well. Now normally like
stronger growth is good right but the
market in this market weird news is bad
because that means the Fed might rate
hikes uh or keep the rates for higher
for longer uh which is not what we want
in this environment because of all the
buildout that we have to you know has to
take place on that. So yesterday because
of all that um uh we had a bit of uh bit
of a sell-off and also keep in mind that
yesterday we had fed officials some of
the fed officials came out and saying
that AI infrastructure buildout could
create near-term inflation as well which
I don't which which I don't
>> sort of with like memory right memory
power like there are things that you're
starting to see that with like our
laptops are now have gone up what 20%.
>> Exactly. But today we're seeing the
opposite of that, right? Like OpenAI,
like Kyle mentioned, just hit 70 billion
in ARR reportedly. Um, that's just
showing us how much the demand is
growing. They were at 20 billion in
2025, end of 2025. They were just at 45
billion a month ago. Now they're at 70
billion, which is crazy. And what they
said was interesting was enterprise is
now its fastest growing B2B uh revenue
and it's up more than 700% since July.
So this is this is this is crazy. Yes.
And um another thing is like we have
tomorrow we have micron earnings come up
which is going to be a huge maybe a
catalyst for the market as well. Uh but
overall I I think this is we I remain
extremely bullish. I think the macro is
starting to concern me a bit, especially
the rates. But hopefully Besson and and
the team will figure that out soon. Even
like mortgage rates are you might even
see 8% interest rate mortgage rates by
next week. I hope it doesn't happen, but
it seems like we're headed that way. But
so yeah, remain overall bullish on the
entire market, but macro is starting to
scare me.
>> Marin, what do you think? Yeah, I have
been um a little bit more bearish over
the last few weeks and the reason is I
like I'm bullish compute but I I don't
think like everything is just dependent
on you know ongoing capex thing and if I
see some breaks underneath the like the
economy then it makes me worried and so
like look at the you know um airlines or
machinery or homebuilders or like even
the Russell 2000 like it's going down
and down only. So it like it doesn't
tell me that the whole economy is doing
well and I don't think that like if
retail and everyone else is is not going
to do well then the ongoing copex thing
is going to just push everything you
know higher forever. So right now I
think that you know yields are at record
highs. Oil is elevated again and so
there are different things that doesn't
look really good [clears throat] and
constructive for the markets at the
moment. So I have 20% in cash and I'm
actually considering to like maybe the
risk a bit more even.
>> How do you think about you know there's
all this bad news out there right now
with rates with oil etc. Yet, the S&P
500 and the NASDAQ are what, like 5%
from all-time highs. Maybe not even 5%,
maybe less than that. And so, it's like
I understand there's all this bad news
out there, but then markets, at least in
some parts of the markets, like you
said, it's not everything, but in some
parts of the market, they're holding up
strong. Uh, and then, you know, so is is
is the bad news already kind of priced
in and the market's kind of shaking off
and doesn't care, or is there a lag in
the market? It needs to catch up to the
bad news. like which which way do you
think it's going? Martin, we'll start
with you. Melvin, maybe you've got a
thought on this too.
>> Yeah, I think everyone is just so
focused on the AI trade and just like I
am on the same trade. Like I think the
demand for compute is just going to
accelerate from here. But it doesn't
mean that S&P and NASDAQ will just keep
you know doing new all-time highs. So
like I think now I believe when we see
like red days like yesterday on S&P or
NASDAQ then the the the further down we
go the more obvious it becomes that like
okay AI trade is doing well but the rest
of the market is not. So like maybe it's
really a good time to derisk. So I think
that the the the market optimism will
eventually like try to look at the raw
data and see like oh okay maybe like we
are not just mooning and just up only
from here.
>> The thing is the market's not super
bullish right now either though like if
you look at the sentiment and stuff it's
it's actually fairly bearish. Um yet
prices is
>> we at all times and you say that
sentiment is bearish. I don't get it. it
is. Well, sentiment and price are two
completely different things and
oftentimes they diverge. But if you look
at the sentiment indicators, they are
not euphoric or at what they would think
they would be from all-time highs. And
so I just like I'm just trying to
understand the divergence here because
there there definitely is. And it's it's
quite interesting to see. I don't know,
Melvin, you have any thoughts on this?
>> Yeah, I mean like yes, market is
bearish, but I think we're moving with
caution, right? like if if if there
there's not too much euphoria in the AI
market right now. I feel like um I think
investors are starting to, you know, get
worry. I think we need like next
earnings to prove that, you know, we
need, you know, we're going to go
higher. Um I think the great catalyst
would be like Muse and um like Meta
coming out saying that Muse is going to,
you know, um access their growth and you
know, like anthropic IPO. I think they
just might have filed some IPO news the
other day. I I I might be mistaken. So,
all that will help build the market up
and I think midterms is right around the
corner. Trump needs a you know strong
stock market um in order for him to like
really have a chance. I don't think he
has a chance to win at the moment the
Republicans, but markets need to stay
elevated for him to even get some seats
or yeah some seats. So, like I think
we're just going to go higher. I think
Besson and his team will eventually
figure out the rates though. I there's
no there's no way because US need to
refinance almost $10 trillion in debt
this year and they're not going to
refinance it at seven or eight%. That is
crazy. So he needs the yields to come
down and hopefully he will be able to do
that.
>> We're going to pause for a second. The
AI trade is changing. The bottleneck
stocks are either running out of steam
or getting ready for another leg higher
while the application layer is finally
starting to show some real profits. Our
analysts were early to the last wave and
now they are buying for the next one.
Catch your next call inside Milkroad Pro
for just a dollar at the link below.
>> I feel like we're we're climbing a wall
of worry where it's just there's just
all this bad news thrown at it and the
market just doesn't care because the
growth is so big, right? Like if we go
to GDP, there's been multiple so I think
it was Elon said the other day um he
expects us to double GDP from 2% to 4%
next year. Uh even um I'm not sure who
it was, but a politician or someone on
the Fed or whatever also said they
expect 4% next year as well. Uh he
tweeted out this morning. Um I don't
have the name, but um I I find it hard
to see the market struggle in a time
where we're going to double GDP. Now,
obviously, it's not for sure we're going
to double GDP, but I think it's pretty
clear earnings are going a lot higher.
Um and so um GDP is likely to grow
significantly and so it's hard to say um
that we're going to have at least a
accelerated or or sorry not accelerated
but a long-term bare market or anything
like that. Like Martin I assume you're
just expecting a pullback and then a
quick recovery or are you expecting
something more drawn out and we go into
like a 22 2022 long bare market?
>> I don't know. Like I don't have a strong
view how this is going to play out but I
think some correction uh is on the
horizon for sure. I think there's
absolutely no way we can have a drawn
out uh bare market at this at this pace
of growth. Um because it's it's it's not
just growth of capex, it is growth of
revenues. I mean, you just saw OpenAI go
from 40 billion to 70 70 billion in like
a month and a half. They added 30
billion in ARR in a month and a half.
These numbers are actually in insane. Um
and then on top of that, you have
Enthropic, which is still growing. It's
not as as much, but it's still growing.
I think they're 75 billion. Um, but now
you also have Grockbot, which I'm sure
has added billions in their ARR as a
result of of Grockbot and Gro 4.6. Um,
Muse, I don't know because I think it's
mostly free at the moment. So, I'm not
sure they're going to see a ton of
growth in revenue yet. Um, but that's
okay. So, we're just we're seeing a lot
of growth on the on the revenue side.
Um, which just leads me to believe that
this market has to go higher at some
point. Maybe there's a pullback in
sight. I don't know. Vincent just joined
in. What's up, brother? Uh we're talking
market right now. Give us your quick
take and then we're going to move into
some AI stuff.
>> I mean my view is that the numbers from
today
took the risk off in terms of there is
an issue for frontier. I think you guys
just discussed it. I think from from
entropic perspective the key number is
those or are those 518 billion kind of
implanted AI infrastructure spent and
80% of that is kind of committed. uh and
you talked about the so so yeah
yesterday I was writing on X that this
is the key risk today it was taken off
the table it was bad timing I guess uh
but for me those numbers are proving
that um yeah market is still healthy
regard
>> you guys know what was the biggest
driver of like open AI recent like
revenue spike it was Astra it was Astra
>> well yeah
>> and yesterday Codex yeah but like people
are using Astra like the most of audio
models and like yesterday Claude
announced Sonet 5.5 which is five times
cheaper and like even more performant
than Astra. So like you know it's it's a
game of like just showing higher number
I feel like but like
>> yeah but nobody cares about the number.
Nobody nobody cares about the number.
Nobody cares. All they need is a good UX
and a good UI to run their business
inside of these platforms and they'll
pay the money. That's it. It doesn't
matter how smart the model is. It
doesn't matter how cheap it is. It just
matters. Does it work for what I need?
And so like I, you know, they can keep
pushing out these different models and
then people post these pictures that it
or these videos of it doing this thing.
Doesn't matter. People just need a place
where they can put their company and
their team inside of it so they can use
AI and they can have agents and they can
connect to the platforms that they use
and the software tools they use and they
can get the work streams they need and
the automated flows. And as long as that
works, they'll pay the money because
it's allowing their businesses to be way
more efficient. That's all that matters.
>> But you will optimize for cost
eventually like everyone does. So it's
pretty clear. But I mean you guys are
just like, you know, highlighting the
high like the numbers you see like
revenues. I can like boost our revenues
if I want to, but we don't know how much
money they spend on training those
models, how much money they spend on
inference. is I would bet it's not even
profitable at this point because like
and yesterday one of the product
managers in open AAI announced that
they're going to reduce the subscription
token usage. So because right now they
are subsidizing subscriptions by a a
ton. So it's changing as well. So
there's a lot of pressure and like
everyone is talking AR that it's
increasing. That's great. But do you
know how much money they have to spend
every year to stay at the frontier? No.
Do you know how much money they spend
subsidizing all the usage today? No. So
like we get only like a little like
piece of it
>> only. Yeah. Like only small piece of
information. Well, they're probably
about to sign even more deals because uh
today is OpenAI's dev dev day. And last
year, I don't know if you guys remember
last year, OpenAI announced that um six
gigawatts of AMD GPUs with uh you know,
with AMD, they signed a massive deal and
AMD jumped 24% um last year. So, we will
likely see more commitments and more
deployment of capital like in the in the
in today. So,
>> so here we go. So just launched right
now the devs day for open AI is going on
right now. Open eye just launched dots
which is their always on AI agents
inside chat GBT powered by Astra. So
this is Grockbot or Muse. You now have
that inside of um ChatgBT. It gets its
own cloud computer, its own browser
access. Uh it can connect to everything,
you know, thousands of apps, all the
things that already had. Um it's
basically Grockbot but now inside of of
OpenAI. So that's the first thing that
they just launched. Um, I'll keep an eye
to see if there's anything else going
on, but um, agents are here. We we've
been talking about this all year,
consumer agents, uh, and enterprise
agents actually. And, um, and they are
no doubt here. And I, the reason why I'm
still bullish on the market is I think
agents are way more capable than what
chat was. Um, and you can do so much
more. Like a lot of people I'm seeing in
my team who they never really touched
agents in terms of like using Hermes or
OpenClaw, they're like addicted to Muse
or to Grockbot and they're able to do so
much more now. I'm using uh Grockbot
like crazy, spending way more. Uh and I
just think there's so much more usage
now that we have these kind of always on
agents. Um now I the question is that
Martin brings up is is it profitable? Um
which to be honest it doesn't need to be
I don't think. Um, but I think like
Enthropic showed profit last quarter and
there was rumors that OpenAI was going
to show profit this quarter Q um Q3 and
I would say there's probably no doubt
that's going to happen after this
growth. Like they just had $30 billion
in AR in in like a month and a half.
You've you've these numbers are nothing
like anyone's ever seen before. That's
an absolute insane number. Um, but I
would imagine they are close to
profitable if not profitable uh this
quarter. My view is that I think the
market doesn't care too much about
profitability at this stage. I think the
market cares more about growth. Yes,
this was also my major concern and
that's why this was alleviated today a
lot there. There there were two numbers
in
>> Sorry, keep going. I just was let me
just say one thing before [laughter] you
say this. Chatbt has now reached 1.2 2
billion weekly users and more than 2.5
million businesses.
>> These numbers are [laughter] insane.
>> How many businesses?
>> 2.5 million businesses.
>> Insane.
>> Insane. Yeah.
>> Staggering growth. No, the the the two
core numbers that from the entropic kind
of Reuters IPO perspect that catch my
focus was one the the 518 billion that I
was talking about earlier and then
number two that 25% of the revenue came
from two customers only my guess is it's
Microsoft that's pretty clear and then
the second one is probably cursor but
don't know um those are end of 2025
numbers and the issue I see there it's
If if that is still the case today and
obviously we know that Curser is
integrated by by SpaceX now then Curser
could eventually move some of that
entropic demand towards uh SpaceX and
could take off a lot of revenue from
from SpaceX from from Entropic at once
that that's a risk I see. And then the
final point I I heard a podcast this
week where where the speaker was arguing
that 25% of frontier AI revenue is
coming from basically startups that are
f that are uh funded by venture money.
And as we are potentially going into a
rate hike cycle, this could obviously
hit the whole venture funding cycle and
therefore uh cycle through the the the
revenue for Frontier. I found that
really interesting. Now, I don't think
that's the base case today, but I'm
still in the camp of of Martin that
there are some risks regarding Frontier.
And if you have a a very heavy
allocation to it, like maybe 40 50 60%
plus across your entire portfolio, it
makes sense to take some chips off the
table.
>> Even if if the the that revenue moves
from Enthropic over to XAI, it's still
it's still a frontier model generating
the revenue. It's not the revenue is
going away, right? So, is that really a
risk? I mean it's a risk anthropic don't
get me wrong um but like as long as
someone's getting that revenue then is
there really an issue
>> problem I I get what you're coming from
but the problem is that semi analysis
outlined this the opening on a tropic of
buying 40 to 50% of the compute next
year and even if there's no real impact
just the expectation from investors
could trigger the selloff right
>> yeah but so that was before they
launched Grockbot launched and muse
launched and so like okay 40 50%
whatever the number is that they're
going to buy all the new compute coming
online next year. Well, if that all of a
sudden changes and now it's 50 to 60% of
OpenAI, Anthropic, SpaceX or XAI, sorry,
and uh and Meta, is that an issue? Like
just because their share goes down a
little bit because two other bigger
companies with bigger budgets, right,
bigger ability to pay, that seems like a
good thing. Like I'd rather go from two
to four and the other two that are added
in have other revenue streams like
rocket launches and Starlink or you know
multiundred billion dollar ad business
rather than relying on the open AI and
anthropics. So I actually think this is
a good um uh development rather than a
bad development. You know
>> I fully agreed. I think diversifying the
customer base in terms of who's buying
compute is a real good thing. The
question is if there's an issue with
Frontier AI,
>> are the agentic use cases from all the
other companies filling the gap that
could potentially um yeah
increase or or exist if if Frontier gets
damaged. I don't know. Really depends on
the adoption of of Metamuse, Grockbot
and all those other use case, right?
It's an unknown. It's it's it's a risk
factor in the market that Yeah. that we
cannot answer today. I I think I think
there's a there's actually someone who's
in really in trouble right now. A sector
I think I'm still going to argue about
this. I think it's it's software.
Software stocks is getting ready for a
round two selloff. We saw this happen
earlier this year when Anthropic went
after all these legal services,
financial services, enterprise, blah
blah blah. Now Meta, Muse, and Grock is
going after enterprise value. And what
does that mean? That means that because
earlier this week we saw that Meta
launch meta enterprise platform uh which
you know directly goes into uh other
businesses and they can connect tools
and whatnot and then Grock is after
going after to gro business and um their
side of things. So eventually we will
have claude and all these all these
companies will go after software and I
think software problem gets much bigger
because right now right like if you use
Salesforce for CRM service now for
workflows yada yada yada you're going to
be using agents and telling agents to
use those system for you. So they're so
they a lot of those traditional
businesses work on seat per head you
know like how much pe how many people
actually use it. Now if agents are using
on their behalf, the whole business
model get in like disrupted and also yes
they're using it for usage and whatnot
but I think there's no way for these
companies to be actually profitable or
in the long term if they don't actually
start to go after these uh services. So
I think this is just going to decimate
these some of these uh software names
once again we're going to we're going to
see another sell off and we saw that
actually yesterday with Muse when they
launched enterprise they the software
stocks already dropped 3 to 4%. So you
think like they're going to rebuild like
Service Now and Salesforce? I
>> So it's interesting. So here's my take.
Um I don't So SAS is not dead by any
means. I think we need more SAS as a
result of using agents, right? Like we
need more software. Okay. Now I do agree
Melvin some SAS products that exist out
there that you do pay for you either
don't need anymore or the big risk is
that you know entropic and open AI start
to basically rebuild the SAS tools and
have them already integrated in. So like
there is disruption there but I don't
think it's a catchall like we don't need
SAS anymore because agents are just
going to you know build all or like AI
is going to build all the s software for
us and we don't need it. That's
definitely not a case. we're still going
to pay for software, but I do agree we
might just pay for that software inside
of OpenAI or inside of Enthropic or
inside of Grockbot as they start to
disrupt certain areas. Um, but I do
think there's many software companies
that are smart and have already pivoted
like you just talked about the seats
versus usage. Salesforce has already
built Agent Force and now they're
focused on on usage. It's their fastest
growing product by a long shot. Um,
they're integrating agents into Slack.
Uh, you just saw Grockbot. uh you can
now launch it inside of Slack. So like
there there are there are certain
software companies that are ahead of the
game and they're are building for this
agentic world and then there are others
that maybe are slower and not so much
and that could be a problem. Um, but I
do think what happens here is there's
because of AI and because of agents,
there's more businesses than ever
before. And that is literally hockey
stick curve up up like this. And if
there's more businesses, it means that
there's more SAS products needed, right?
There's more content creators, there's
more businesses, there's more all the
things like entrepreneurs than ever
before, which means there's more SAS
needed than ever before. And so I think
there's a lot of SAS companies that are
actually doing really well because of
agents. Um, but I do agree there is some
risk to certain products. I don't know
exactly which ones yet because I do
think OpenAI or or Enthropic will need
to become part of the app layer rather
than just the like you know right now
they sell tokens and that's you know
that's the disruption Martin's talking
about and it's a good business right now
but as we've talked about for months now
there's pressures there and so they're
going to need to start to build on the
application layer which is right now a
lot of companies are taking advantage of
kind of this like reselling tokens right
uh and I think I think they're going to
eventually do that I just don't know
which ones they'll go after first.
>> But the problem
>> design appears to be it is is a big one
they're going after.
>> But the I think the main problem is we
don't know who's who's likely going to
be the winner. That's the problem.
Market's just going to group all these
companies together and sell off all all
of them together like we saw this
earlier this year and then we had a big
drop. Now even the stocks hasn't even
largely recovered. If you look at stocks
like you know there's a lot of stocks
that are down 50 60% even the good ones
you know. So that's that's my main worry
in the short term for software stocks.
>> I agree. I think that the frontier labs
really need to move in the stack up and
so really like bring those like returns
to the companies but what's their kind
of advantage like because if I'm
Salesforce I have already I'm integrated
everywhere so it's just much easier for
me to hey guys like we have all your
data so let let us build your agents or
like you know we even have our own
language model so like what is cloud
going to bring like what's your value
proposition like
>> I mean they're also getting integrated
everywhere too like everyone is
integrating into their cloud or into
their open AI
>> but it's different when you just inte
it's it's a different thing if you just
integrate cloud that like hey every
employee can just shed with cloud that's
a different thing than if you integrate
with like service now or Salesforce
those are like just data companies that
like work like no other
>> it's just much more embedded in your
business
>> where I think the the one second Vincent
where I think the frontier models are
going is so right now there's there's
the model layer where they basically
sell tokens they can either go up the
stack to the application layer that's
what we're talking about or they can do
what SpaceX and Meta are doing which is
go down the stack and just build the
infrastructure and and then they can
resell it or use it themselves and have
that optionality that's what I love
about SpaceX SpaceX is going you know
instead of just being this they're going
down the stack into the infrastructure
layer I think um someone from ARC put
out that they're they expect uh SpaceX
to have 66.6 gawatts of compute by 2031.
And Elon commented and said, "I'd be
disappointed if that's how low we were."
I was [laughter] like, "What? 66 gawatt.
They're currently at like 1.4."
[laughter]
So it So they're going the other side.
Uh but I bet you they go both. I think
they're going to build for both, too. Um
which is going to put them in a crazy
position. Um, but we'll see if if OpenAI
and Enthropic do that or not. Right now,
they're not going down the stack.
They're only going up the Well, my
assumption is they're going to go up the
stack. Vincent, you were gonna say
something, then Martin, we'll let you
jump in. So, I agree with Melvin to a
certain extent. I've [snorts]
I would not be surprised if there is a
sell-off in SAS because the market these
days is really scared and also to a
certain extent stupid. Um,
I would agree then or I would think
about this as a buy the dip then because
I fully agree with both of you Kyle and
Martin as well that SAS is not dead and
those agents will use the existing um
software layers that exist right because
there is also think about it from an
efficiency point of view. We are in a
compute constrained world. Why would any
agent have the idea of build their own
software if there is an existing one
they can use? They are rational things,
right? They would not do that. So my
view is that agents will use legacy
software a lot. Yes, some of it will be
destroyed, but most of it that's
actually valuable that's open for agents
to to to be accessed. those will survive
and and actually flourish because there
will be will be billions and eventually
trillions of agents.
>> Yeah, I just wanted to say that like
eventually at some point I think like
hyperscalers like and like SpaceX and
like anthropic they will all converge to
the same business model. they have the
compute they will have their own models
and then they will also kind of do the
the harness and also like sell agents
and like because agents are ultimately
replacing humans and that's the whole
thing right so I think in 10 years like
pretty much everyone will converge to to
to like be part of like the whole stack
but what does that mean then what is the
mode in that world then
>> the mode is is the ability to build the
infrastructure ructure which is SpaceX.
They have the large like if you just
think long term enough it's SpaceX has
the biggest mode of them all because
they have the ability to to um to build
data centers here. They have the ability
to put them up in space which no one
else has. Uh and they're building
terafab which will be the largest uh
production of chips in I don't know if
it's bigger I think it's in the world at
least for sure in the US. Um and so the
only person that's building for the
biggest mode is is SpaceX Elon. Um, so I
think SpaceX and Tesla will be set up,
but that's obviously a long-term thing.
It's if you think more meta about the
market.
>> Speaking of uh SpaceX a bit, did you
guys see the um data that came out or
news that came out by information this
morning that um initially SpaceX signed
a deal with Anthropic worth only about
45 billion. Now they're saying that
Anthropic actually signed a deal worth
up to 84 billion uh with SpaceX to use
their orbital computer or orbital data
centers, you know,
>> terrestrial on Earth, not not on space.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Sorry. Um Yeah. So like
imagine that that was not, you know,
that was not factored in. This is new
news and SpaceX is running because of
that right now.
>> Elon also mentioned the timelines of
their buildout right now for compute. So
the expectation was going to be 2
gawatts of compute by the end of the
year. It looks like it's going to be
2.6. So they're ahead of schedule which
is absolutely insane. And they're
already got concrete down for Terraab.
These guys are just like lightning
speed. It's unbelievable.
>> Martin, what do you think the motives in
that world? Do you think there's
anything else when when all the
companies are essentially moving up the
stack? Yeah, I think each company will
be able to capture their market share
from different layer and then they will
just grow up and down and it will help
them to like have some market share
>> physical integration.
>> Okay.
>> I think that data is how how they will
differentiate from each other, right? I
think you can tell by what Figure is
doing, what Eli Liy is doing, what
Bending Spoons is doing. They're all
are are striving for more data. Tesla is
doing the same. And if you're the one
that can provide the most context or
most data points to that fancy AI
infrastructure layer to the agents
eventually, I think you can build the
best products and services for for
people.
>> It's data and compute because if you
have a bunch of data but you have no
compute, you can't do anything with that
data.
>> So it's who has the most data, who has
the most compute. Um like that that it's
those two things are everything moving
forward, right? Because if AI is
everything, which we all agree with,
agents are going to be what does
everything moving forward. Then you need
data for those agents to do things. You
need compute to actually process that
data. If you don't have those two, if
you don't have the compute, you can't do
anything with that data.
>> Did I just hear a bull case for Meta
here?
>> For Meta SpaceX. Yeah, for sure.
>> Have you guys seen that uh Amazon uh
Jeff Bezos uh raised another money for
Blue Origin?
I think it was subscribed like 15 times
or something and the valuation is 150
billion I believe. So
>> why
>> but
>> he's got no shot.
[laughter]
>> I think he's got no shot, dude. Like if
you seen that like Starship launch, was
it yesterday? This is insane, right? And
these guys like it's so much bigger and
better than every other product out
there. And the next uh I don't know when
the next launch is of it, but they're
going to try and catch it. And it'll be
fully reusable, which is just no one's
even remotely close to doing what SpaceX
trying to do.
>> Literally a decade away, bro, from what
Elon's doing right now. They're not.
>> Um All right, let's talk Micron. So
Micron's going to start off the Q3
earnings season, which kicks off
Wednesday. Um I don't know how Micron
got first spot, but that's that's nice.
Uh pretty much first spot, first for any
of the important companies. Um, Melvin,
what's your take on what's going to
happen uh I guess everyone's watching
this on Wednesday, so tonight uh in Q3
earnings Micron.
>> Yeah, so I actually just posted a note
last night um about Micron. Wall Street
is on our pro platform. Um Wall Street
is expecting roughly 51 billion in
revenue and around 31 to 30 31ish EPS.
Um my estimate is around 52.2 2 billion
in revenue with the 8 87.5 gross margin.
I think it's because the reason why mine
is a little bit higher than the Wall
Street is because demand is just
accelerating. Um I think the margins are
actually improving. I think um the
long-term supply that they're signing
are just going to massively rerate this
stock I believe in in the next coming in
coming days. Um I the key things that
I'm watching out for is um I want them
to address um about supply coming
online. How much supply is coming
online? I I want them to talk about the
memory uh manufacturers in China and
address that once and for all. I'm not
super worried about like whether that's
going to make an impact on HBM supply.
It's not it's not going to make an
impress but I would it would be nice to
hear about that. I also want to hear
about their pipeline. Um they just
started um work shipping I think HBM 3 4
HBM4. I want to see how they're doing
with that. And there there's a bunch of
things I'm watching out for. Most
importantly, I want to know how many
more long-term agreements they have
signed this this this time around. Last
last time it was around 16. Um it would
be nice to get at least more than that
this time around to, you know, just once
and for all um kill that narrative that
you know this business is cyclical. Like
I'm tired of hearing that. I think if
they could address this once overall, u
this would be great. But overall, I
remain bullish. I think they're going to
have a blowout numbers, but uh the stock
it's always a coin toss up. We we see
that time and time again. I I really
don't know which way it's going to move.
Hopefully up. I
>> I think at this point, everyone knows
that its earnings are going to be
incredible. So, I don't think earnings
is really going to move the needle for
for this. It's more just the the risks
on the back end.
>> Yeah. Well, guidance, sure. And then
also just the risks on the back end
around OpenAI entropic. like I feel like
that's all that matters at the moment
for this stuff.
>> I disagree with that. I think the
outlook especially in memory is core. I
I fully agree with you Melvin that
the management needs to do a good job in
terms of convincing investor that this
is not cyclical anymore. Maybe they can
show more long-term agreements or we
know they have like 16 long-term
agreements um through 2027 and 2028. We
just need to understand what's kind of
the base in terms of their revenue and
the margins they have in those long-term
agreements and how much of capacity is
in those long-term agreements. Right?
That's what we need to understand. And
this number one and then number two,
2028 there's a lot of supply coming
online. Is this hitting their margin and
their revenue or not? Those are the two
things I'm looking forward. I fully
agree this once again will be a blowoff
quarter which will not move the stock.
>> Yeah, there's there's actually news that
came out the other day that Samsung
customers are actually looking for deals
for more than 10 years now. They want to
sign more than 10year deals with
Samsung. We're talking to like 2035,
man, or 2036, which is crazy. This is
this is going to give them so much
visibility and um you know really kill
that narrative, you know, if they're
start to sign these 10-year deals. So
hopefully,
>> yeah, but get some of that.
>> It pushes you in a in a pretty tricky
situation as SKHX and the because you
need it's the same as the NeoClouds. You
need to decide are you selling now
basically for a lower price that you're
committed into the next 10 years or and
and how much of spare capacity do you
leave for kind of flexible allocations
that you can sell at the higher price
and higher margin. Right? It's it's it's
tricky
>> but it's better because like they are
selling to profitable companies versus
if you are you know new clouds you are
selling to open AI anthropic and others
[clears throat] and they're not
profitable or barely profitable.
>> Yeah.
>> Um but I actually heard that like the
whole Korean memory uh supply is locked
in till 2031 like like 100%.
That's that's just insane. Like why
these stocks are not up like I don't
know 200x
or 200%. Sorry. It's like doesn't make
sense. So what I would actually expect
from all these memory uh stocks when
they have their earnings call they
should start talking about buybacks and
like making sure that investors are
happy and they see the success of the
company in some materialized way either
dividends or buybacks just do something
because it trades at stupidly cheap
prices right now and like they should do
something about that. I mean the thing
is like can buybacks even make a
meaningful supply uh like change in the
earnings because we saw like um uh
Nvidia right they announced 150 billion
in buybacks they're going to buy back
almost 250 billion over the next like
couple years or over the next 18 months
sorry um and like the stock has not
moved up like literally has not moved up
>> yeah but buybacks are over 18 months
right it's not just it doesn't just pump
because of the news that they're going
to buy back. It's a $5 trillion stock,
right? Like it's just now there's upward
pressure put on the stock over time,
which is what's going to happen uh with
well Micron can't do buybacks till
December. Um but I think [clears throat]
some of the others can start it earlier.
>> Yeah. And you see it in the reported
earnings per share per quarter. That's
where you see the impact in the end
because you have a lower share that you
the share amount you divide the EPS is
lower. So
>> So it's always like the the buyback size
relative to your market cap, right? Like
if you can buy 10% of your like the
whole market then like it's obviously
going to move the price.
>> Yeah. And remember that the UBS analysis
where they said but that was at lower
prices. So probably the number is lower
now but they said I think two months ago
or so said 40%. It's like at at the cash
flow rates of M they can buy back 40% of
flowing stock. I mean that would drive
earnings per share up. It's actually,
yeah, the number is even better now
because when they said that, Micron was
at all-time highs. Uh, and now I think
the expectation is that the revenue is
even higher than it was previously. So,
the free cash was even better because
all of a sudden now people realize the
margins are going to last for the next,
you know, till 2029, 2030, whatever. Uh,
all right guys, we've got to we've got
to wrap up and um and move to the after
hours. By the way, one thing I just saw
on Twitter here is um SpaceX dot.com for
the DOT launch of of ChatBT. So, if you
go to dots.com, it goes to goes to
Grockpots's landing page.
>> No, [laughter]
they're pushing it all over X right now,
which is hilarious.
>> Oh, man. Such a meme world. I love it.
All right, guys. Uh, let's uh actually,
anyone have any final final thoughts
they want to say before we jump over to
to the after hours? Is there anything we
we missed yet? I think we did not,
unless you guys did in the beginning,
but meta really moves into a spot where
I get interesting because the entire
year my argument was they're spending
money and we do not know what they're
doing with the compute they're buying.
But now it gets clearer and clearer that
they want to move in the whole agentic
side, both consumer and enterprise now.
Um, and obviously the revenues from that
could get crazy at some point in time.
So yeah.
>> Yeah. But the stock's up like 45% in two
weeks. Is he going to buy that?
>> I mean, I haven't looked in in like I
know of course what Meta is, but like in
terms of how big the enterprise cycle
gap, but then also
>> is there a risk for the ad side of
business uh because of the agents
themselves. That's some that's kind of
the core risk I see at the moment for
>> for Meta. But honestly, I think it's
such a misconception when stocks are up,
you cannot buy into them. There is a
great I don't know who said that but
someone from the startup world who said
when a probably [laughter] not
when a stock is up like 100% or 200% the
the the upside is is usually much bigger
because the market is onto something and
it's not the full story yet. Um so yeah
Melvin, you're a Meta owner. You got
anything to add here?
>> Man, I'm happy happy that Vince is
finally coming around. I've been arguing
this the whole year, but I know
seriously like the market was wary of
what Meta was doing for good reasons. I
think Zuck is really starting to turn
this around. And what I actually like
about Zuck and how he's approaching this
entire AI debate is that Zuck actually
went on a couple podcasts and was very
rational with what he's saying about AI
and his viewpoints on Daario and um you
know and the entire AI world is that
Meta actually did not release this Muse
model like they could have released it
two months ago but Zuck made sure that
you know they were trustworthy before
that they release it out in the into the
you know into the world. Um, so I really
like that Zuck is, you know, actually
starting to realize that trust is
[laughter]
>> trust is actually a big moat in this in
this world though because if you if
consumers and if your businesses cannot
trust your product, you will not get
adopted in in the world. So like I I
think Zuck is actually making a really
good stride towards that.
>> The biggest advantage I think is
distribution that Meta has. They have a
way better distribution than chat GBT,
OpenAI, Grockport or any of their peers.
I mean how many billion or million
businesses and how many billion
individual peoples do they have on their
platforms and they can that's all 10
addressable market for them. So that
makes me really bullish
>> and and that is actually very when we
talk about mo it's not like it's part of
a mode as well because like for example
why don't I use Muse because Grockbot is
in my car right it's in my Tesla and so
like when I'm driving to the gym or I'm
driving to the golf course or I'm
driving wherever like I'm I'm talking to
my Grock and I'm using my Grockbot right
and so I'm like I just I actually I I
think Muse is great. It's the same
thing. I think whatever OpenAI is
probably doing with DOTS is probably
going to be great but it's like well the
devices that I use which is I use
Twitter and I use my my Tesla it's like
well if Grockbots's already integrated
to those I'm just going to use that and
so Muse has that same benefit with if
you're a big Instagram WhatsApp threads
Facebook user um then you sort of get
that benefit as well right which is the
one thing that like Enthropic Chachi or
OpenAI don't have um but these other
companies they do have this right and
this is why I still think Apple and
Google can do something. I don't know if
they will. They seem to not want to do
anything. I actually tried to use I
use Siri yesterday when I was like
making a recipe and I asked it a
question and I like my hands were dirty
cuz I was like mixing up something and
Siri comes back. I asked it a
question just like a all I wanted to do
was like convert grams into pounds or
something like that and it's like do you
want me to ask chat GBT or should I
browse the internet and I was like I
don't give a Just give me the
answer. Like what are you asking me that
for like what is going on? And then I
was like browse and then it goes I have
to put in my pin code to open up the
phone [laughter] so it go and I was like
what is going so I had to ask Google
because I have a Google Home in my
kitchen. I had to ask that cuz Apple was
completely useless. I was like how is it
2026 Meta's launching this stuff? X is
launching this stuff and this is what
Apple has. It's insane. Um
>> yeah but what's pretty obvious is Apple
will come out with a similar product
right because their distribution
advantages.
>> Yeah. But now they have a CEO who's
who's having tech and engineering
background. And there there was some
news I think today or yesterday where
where they were talking about the
release cadence of new products. Um and
yeah,
>> I've been calling for this all year and
thankfully Apple's at all-time highs,
but [laughter] were not why I thought it
would be.
Anyway, all right, let's jump into the
after hours because there was actually
some really big moves in the portfolio.
One today uh and a few others this week
that we need to break down. And so we're
going to jump into the after hours. For
those that are listening, you can come
and join us. After hours is just a show
that we do after this where the four of
us are going to talk about our
portfolios. We'll share it on screen. Um
you can see everything inside of our
portfolio and we're going to talk about
the moves that we make. It's a dollar to
check it out. So if you want to watch
this after hours video, it's $1. Just go
to milkroad.com/pro.
Uh and you can check it out. Thanks
everyone for listening and we'll see you
guys at the after hours.
>> Thanks for listening to Milk Road.
[music] If you enjoyed the show, make
sure you like and subscribe. And if
you're struggling to find winners in the
market, that's exactly what Milkroad Pro
is built [music] for. Our analysts have
called some of the biggest winners
early, and Pro lets you see what they're
buying next, every trade they make, and
the research behind every position.
[music] Check out Milk Road Pro at the
link below. Everything you hear on Milk
Road is forformational purposes only.
These are our personal opinions, not
financial advice, and we may own some of
the investments we talk about. Always do
your own research and make the decisions
that are right for you. See you next
time.